landofbasketball.com 2019-03-30

# LandOfBasketball.com Privacy Policy

## **Privacy Policy**

**LandOfBasketball.com** and its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below there is information on what types of personal data we receive and collect when you visit and use our website.

### **Cookies**

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile device by almost all the websites that you visit. They are used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide traffic information to the owners of the site. Cookies are just strings of text and numbers and they are not programs and therefore cannot contain viruses or other malicious software.

We use cookies **to ensure that we give you the best experience** on our website. Rest assured that **LandOfBasketball.com does not use cookies to store or collect any kind of personal information**.

We also use third party services for statistis, advertising and social network functions. These services use their own cookies to function properly.

By using this website you are consenting to our use of the cookies outlined here, including third party cookies. Details about third party cookies and about how to control and delete cookies are listed below.

### **Statistical Service**

The statistical service we use, [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics/index.html), uses cookies to collect anonymous traffic data to provide us information such as visited pages, referring URLs, browser used and other publicly available data. This data does not contain information that allows us to personally identify you in any way. You can read more about how this statistical service works at [Google's own privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

### **Third Party Advertising, Cookies and Web Beacons**

To support **LandOfBasketball.com** we use third-party advertising companies such as [Google AdSense](https://www.google.com/adsense/) to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use general information (not including personal data like your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you (these are usually called "personalized" ads). If you would like learn more about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used, you can go to:   
[Google Privacy and Terms: Advertising and Cookies](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads).

In this website, visitors from countries in which the EU ePrivacy Directive's cookie provisions apply and also those who have disabled personalized Adsense ads are only served with "non-personalized" Adsense ads, which use only contextual information (like the content of the loaded web page) and targeting is not based on the profile or past behavior of the visitor. Please note that the non-personalized ads still require cookies to operate.

This website, **LandOfBasketball.com** , also sometimes uses the services of **other well known and established advertising companies and affiliate programs** for the serving of ads, like CJ Affiliate, Amazon, eBay Partner Network, AllPosters, ShareASale, AvantLink, Affiliate Future, Rakuten, PepperJam and FlexOffers among others. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons (1-pixel transparent images used for tracking) when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers non-personally identifying information. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited. All this companies **have their own privacy policies** , if you want to review them you can follow these links: [CJ Affiliate](https://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy), [Amazon](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp_left_v4_sib?ie=UTF8&nodeId=201909010), [eBay Partner Network](https://partnernetwork.ebay.com/legal/), [AllPosters](https://www.allposters.com/help/guarantee.html#privacy), [ShareASale](https://www.shareasale.com/PrivacyPolicy.pdf), [AvantLink](https://www.avantlink.com/privacy), [Affiliate Future](https://www.affiliatefuture.com/Legal/privacy), [Rakuten](https://www.rakuten.com/legal), [PepperJam](https://www.pepperjam.com/legal), [FlexOffers](https://www.flexoffers.com/).

Another service that uses cookies and web beacons to help us give you a better website experience is AddThis, which provide us with the social media functions: [AddThis Privacy Policy](https://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy/).

**You can chose to disable or selectively turn off cookies** in your browser settings. However, be careful with this because it could affect how you are able to interact with some Internet websites (that's not the case with our website). This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. To learn more about cookies and how to control and disable them you can go to [Cookies and You](https://cookiesandyou.com/).

Although we work only with the best advertising companies and affiliate programs, we are not responsible for the use or data collected in any cookies set by third parties.

### **Spam**

**LandOfBasketball.com** does not send unsolicited e-mail messages that could legitimately be construed as spam. Our advertisers and affiliates are held to the same standards. To be more specific, we only send e-mails to answer questions from our visitors.

### **Logos and Trademarks**

League and team logos and names and all other logos and trademarks belong to their respective owners. This site has no affiliation with any sport Association.

### **Contact**

If you have any comments or questions you can contact us
